Class of 1929 Records, 1925-1994
Smith College Archives
Class of 1929 Records
1925-1994
Smith College. Class of 1929.
RG 80 UUID:00460a65-7c47-41c7-9b2e-5ca22ecbd164
19 boxes (12.7 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1929.
The Class of 1929 was the fifty-first graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1929 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1929, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1929 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Alumnae Leadership Council Reports 1992 (Box 2011, Folder 1)
- Baccalaureate Sunday 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 3)
- Commencement Music 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 4)
- Commencement Photographs 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 5)
- Commencement Speaker 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 6)
- Correspondence (Class Officers) 1954-1964 (Box 2011, Folder 7)
- Correspondence (Class Officers) 1966-1969 (Box 2011, Folder 8)
- Correspondence (Class Officers) 1975-1980, undated (Box 2011, Folder 9)
- Freshman Frolic 1925 (Box 2011, Folder 10)
- Freshman Handbook 1925-1926 (Box 2011, Folder 11)
- Groups 1925-1929 (Box 2011, Folder 12)
- Class Historian 1966-1974 (Box 2011, Folder 13)
- Hoop Rolling 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 14)
- Ivy Day 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 15)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 16)
- Junior Prom 1928 (Box 2011, Folder 17)
- Last Chapel 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 18)
- Class Letters-General 1931-1969 (Box 2011, Folder 19)
- Class Letters-General 1970-1987, undated (Box 2011, Folder 20)
- Class Letters-Alumnae Fund 1930-1958 (Box 2011, Folder 21)
- Class Letters-Alumnae Fund 1959-1982, 1996, undated (Box 2011, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous 1954, 1967, undated (Box 2011, Folder 23)
- Officers 1929 (Box 2011, Folder 24)
- Senior Dramatics 1929 (Box 2010, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1929 (Box 2010, Folder 2)
- Senior Questionnaire 1929 (Box 2010, Folder 3)
- Songs 1925-1929 (Box 2010, Folder 4)
- Sophomore Carnival 1927 (Box 2010, Folder 5)
- Sophomore Push 1927 (Box 2010, Folder 6)
- Step Sings 1929 (Box 2010, Folder 7)
- Class Supper 1929 (Box 2010, Folder 8)
- Reunions-General undated (Box 2013, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1930 (Box 2013, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1934 (Box 2013, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1939 (Box 2013, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1944 (Box 2013, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 2013, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 2013, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 2013, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 2013, Folder 9)
- Reunions-Questionnaire 1964 (Box 2013, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 2013, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 2013, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 2013, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1984 (Box 2013, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2013, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1994 (Box 2013, Folder 16)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-A-Bixler 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 1)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Blanchard-Cohen 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 2)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Connolly-Dunne 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 3)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-East-Grinnan 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 4)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Gilmore-Herold 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 5)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Holden-Kiefer 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 6)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Kirkbride-Manson 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 7)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Martin-Pitts 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 8)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Polacheck-Rogers 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 9)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Rose-Smith 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 10)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Sohst-Thayer 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 11)
- 50th Reunion Questionnaires-Tripp-Zerby 1979 (Box 2014, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary's Records-A-Be (Box 2015, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Records-Bi-Ch (Box 2015, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Records-Cl-E (Box 2015, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Records-F-Go (Box 2015, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Records-Gr-Hi (Box 2015, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Records-Ho-J (Box 2015, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Records-K-L (Box 2015, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Records-M (Box 2016, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Records-N-Ph (Box 2016, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Records-Pi-Ri (Box 2016, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Records-Ro-Sc (Box 2016, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Records-Se-Sq (Box 2016, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Records-St-Z (Box 2016, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box 2016, Folder 7)
- Reunion Scrapbooks and Memorabilia (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box OV)